# **Abdul Ghani Fauzan**

ghani.fauzan11@gmail.com | +6281219477181 | https://ghanfa-portfolio.vercel.app | Linkedin.com/in/ghanfa

# **RINGKASAN**

Lulusan S1 Teknik Informatika dan Bootcamp Front engineer Binar Academy, berpengalaman dalam mengelola usaha swasta maupun digital selama 2 tahun. Memiliki kemampuan dalam Website development terutama Front-end yang berhubungan dengan Javascript. Beminat meniti karier dan mencari kesempatan pada bidang Front end web developer.

### KEMAMPUAN

#### **Hard Skills**

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS Javascript, React. Js, Next. Js Node. Js. Corel, Figma, Photoshop.

#### **Soft Skills**

Problem solving, Adaptasi, Manajemen waktu,

## Kemampuan Bahasa

Bahasa Indonesia, English (TOEFL: 423)

# **PENGALAMAN**

#### Jakarta Repair Sofa – Jakarta, Indonesia

Manajer (Maret 2022 – saat ini)

- Mengelola data administrasi biaya ,
- Pembuatan dokumen perijinan
- Melakukan Survey client dan riset market
- Melakukan pemasaran digital.

#### **Digital Agency**

Desainer Grafis (Juli 2021 – Februari 2022)

- Membuat desain logo untuk keperluan logo pekerja usaha, tim esport indie dll,
- Membuat desain product untuk tas, buku, hijab, banner, poster dll.
- Membuat landing page untuk para pengusaha UMKM.

# Pondok Pesantren Cipari

Staff IT (September 2019 – Juni 2021)

- Memanagement data siswa, Guru, dan Santri
- Menangani berbagai macam permasalahan baik Hardware, Software, dan Network
- Maintenance alat dan asset IT Yayasan,

## PENDIDIKAN & PELATIHAN

### Universitas Pamulang (2016 - 2021)

(S.Komputer -Teknik Informatika) – IPK 3.10/4.00

### FRONT END ENGINEER BOOTCAMP (2023-2024)

Binar Academy

# **Abdul Ghani Fauzan**

ghani.fauzan11@gmail.com | +6281219477181 | https://ghanfa-portfolio.vercel.app/ | Linkedin.com/in/ghanfa

# **SUMMARY**

Graduate of S1 Informatics Engineering and Binar Academy Front Engineer Bootcamp, with experience in managing private and digital businesses for 2 years. Have skills in Website development, especially Front-end related to Javascript. Interested in pursuing a career and looking for opportunities in the front end web developer field.

### **SKILLS**

#### **Hard Skills**

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS Javascript, React.Js, Next.Js Node.Js. Corel, Figma, Photoshop.

#### Soft Skills

Problem Solving, Adaptation, Time Management,

#### Language Skills

Bahasa Indonesia, English (TOEFL: 423)

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Jakarta Repair Sofa – Jakarta, Indonesia

Manager (March 2022 – now)

- Manage financial administration data,
- Creation of licensing documents
- Conduct client surveys and market research
- Do digital marketing.

# **Digital Agency**

Graphic Designer (July 2021 – February 2022)

- Create logo designs for logos for business workers, indie esports teams, etc.
- Create product designs for bags, books, hijabs, banners, posters, etc.
- Create a landing page website for UMKM entrepreneurs.

## **Cipari Islamic School Foundation**

IT staff (September 2019 – Juni 2021)

- Manage student, teacher and student datas
- Handle various kinds of problems both Hardware, Software and Network
- Maintenance of Foundation IT tools and assets,

# **EDUCATION & TRAININGS**

## Pamulang University (2016 - 2021)

(Bachelor of Computer - Informatics Engineering) - GPA 3.10/4.00

### FRONT END ENGINEER BOOTCAMP (2023-2024)

Binar Academy